

Guillem Dolcet

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PHP, Laravel, APIs, SQL, HTML, CSS, JS, Docker, Git, Scrum

Perfil

Programmer with four years of experience in web application development.

Focused on PHP/Laravel but always open to learning new things.

Passionate, communicative, meticulous, and eager to learn

Languages

Catalan - Native

Spanish - Native

English - Conversational

—

Work Experience

2023 - Current

BACKEND DEVELOPER

INSON S.A.

Web development of Backend and Frontend applications with API integration using PHP and Laravel.

2020 - 2023 CompsaOnline S.L. **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

Web development of various Backend

and Frontend applications using PHP,

Laravel, and JS.

Contact

Phone

+34 634 490 171

Email

g.dolcet.jove @gmail.com

Region

Barcelona

Portfolio

guillemdolcet.com

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/guillem-dolcet

Education

2019 - 2021

Higher Degree - Web Applications Development Instutit Almatà

2017 - 2019

Intermediate Degree - Microcomputer Systems and Networks Instutit Almatà